http://www.wga.org/the-guild/privacy-policy

X
Other Searches
Find a WriterSignatory LookupsUndeliverable FundsForeign Levies
Logout
Menu Close
MembersEmployers & AgentsContracts & EnforcementThe GuildNews & EventsWriters' Room
101 Best Lists
What are the best written scripts & shows of all time?
Guilds & Organizations
The Writers Guild of America West website ("Site"), including without limitation, WGAW.ORG, WGAWREGISTRY.ORG, WRITTENBY.COM, and WRITERSGUILDTHEATER.COM are copyrighted ©2016 by the Writers Guild of America West. All rights reserved. Neither the Site nor any part thereof may be reproduced or copied in any form or by any means without the express written consent of the Writers Guild of America West.
Links to Other Internet Sites
At certain places on the Site there may be live "links" to other Internet addresses that can be accessed. Such external Internet addresses contain information created, published, maintained, or otherwise posted by institutions or organizations independent of the Writers Guild of America West ("the Guild"). The Guild does not necessarily endorse, approve, certify, or control these external internet addresses and does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy, timeliness, or correct sequencing of information located at such addresses. Use of any information obtained from such addresses is voluntary, and reliance on it should only be undertaken after an independent review of its accuracy, completeness, efficacy, and timeliness. Reference therein to any specific commercial product, process, or service by trade name, trademark, service mark, manufacturer, or otherwise does not constitute or imply endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by the Guild.
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the Writers Guild of America West's ("the Guild") website ("Site"). Your privacy is important to us. We provide this notice describing our online information practices to keep you informed about how our information is collected and used and to better protect your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by the Guild through WGA.ORG, WGAWREGISTRY.ORG, WRITTENBY.COM, and WRITERSGUILDTHEATER.COM. This policy may differ in some respects from the Guild's policy with regard to personal information collected from its members through other sources.
How We Collect Personal Information and How It Is Used
In general, if you visit our website to access information, you do so anonymously. We do not require you to register or provide personal information (with the exception of the "members-only" area) to view our Site nor do we share or sell any of the information we collect to any ad server companies or other parties. Our Web server will not automatically recognize any visitor's information regarding the domain or email address. The Guild may collect the email or postal addresses of those who communicate with us via email, survey information and/or Site registrations, name and address, telephone number, fax number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address).
Information submitted to the Guild through the Site is kept confidential and is never shared except as required by law. It may at times be used to provide you with further information about the Guild. These communications may be sent by email, postal mail, fax or otherwise. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online. The Guild may collect and share non-identifying and aggregate information, but not personal information with other parties. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, phone number, date of birth, or social security number, and this is not otherwise publicly available.
If you are a member of the Guild registering for the "members-only" area of the Site, you will be required to submit your member number and the last four digits of your social security number. This information is used solely to verify your identity and to provide you with access to the "members-only" area of the Site. We use cookies to store these members' preferences and record user-specific information on what pages visitors access.
When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or employment information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors via a message on our Site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Site.
We also collect and retain personal information when you register material on the Guild's website for the purposes of asserting intellectual property rights or declaring dues or utilizing other website services. When you register we ask you for information such as your name, email address, birth date and zip code. For some services we may also ask for your Social Security number. Once you register with us and sign in to your web site you are not anonymous to us.
If you do not wish to receive communications from the Guild, please send us an email and request that we remove you from any such list. Please note that any request sent pursuant to this paragraph is limited to information you have submitted through the Site. It does not remove you from any other Guild mailing lists.
Upcoming Events
Dec14
Committee of Women Writers Meeting
Dec16
RAMY - A Conversation with Ramy Youssef and Guests
View all Events
Popular Links
Staffing & Development
